<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title> - Articles</title>
    <description>Thoughts of a Once Lost Astronaut</description>
    <link>
    </link>
    
      
      <item>
        <title>De-coupling Angular Component Styles</title>
        
          <description>&lt;!-- https://www.pexels.com/photo/actors-artists-ballet-costumes-45258/ --&gt;

</description>
        
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 13:05:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>
        /de-coupling-angular-component-styles</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/de-coupling-angular-component-styles</guid>
      </item>
      
    
      
      <item>
        <title>Connected Opposites</title>
        
          <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Here’s a poem about dark times, nature &amp;amp; the way forward to happiness&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Memories of years spent in total darkness… have an unique texture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are bumpy, high frequency, turbulent yet not much was done, during the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Day in and day out, going through the motions in an endless ocean… Sinking deeper into an abyss, decorated by feelings of the heart. A recess into another world. An escape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fate. Programming. DNA. Free Will. Choice. Young children, without order, without discipline, are wild, free, and chaotic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As time passes, experience envelopes, like growing trees, networks of neurons, a space growing, a metaphysical world where alone a child, looking down, crying, pain stitched across their face, from a winter’s cold embrace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There, a path required, for a cure desired, has sacrifices to be admired, and as vulnerable as a flower, for series of hours, unless one chooses to sour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Truth may seep in, life’s restoring grace, so happenly, it’s encoded in our place. This place, few ever speak of, is full of life… maybe more than most, but it has no face, it is simply a ghost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you see it, you will not know, it usually introduces itself, like a Christmas coal. A house of wonder, you will not know, maybe there, you will see your midnight glow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But if you are lucky, few dare seek. A fresh flow, you… will… meet.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        
        <pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 15:08:00 -0600</pubDate>
        <link>
        /connected-opposites</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">/connected-opposites</guid>
      </item>
      
    
  </channel>
</rss>
