<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.6.2">Jekyll</generator><link href="/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2018-05-22T19:40:15-06:00</updated><id>/</id><title type="html">Copy &amp;amp; Paste</title><subtitle>Thoughts of a Lost Astronaut</subtitle><entry><title type="html">Connected Opposites</title><link href="/connected-opposites" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Connected Opposites" /><published>2018-05-08T15:08:00-06:00</published><updated>2018-05-08T15:08:00-06:00</updated><id>/connected-opposites</id><content type="html" xml:base="/connected-opposites">&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Here’s a poem, I wrote… about dark memories long ago. If you care to read it, I suggest you read it, very… very… slow.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Memories of years spent in total darkness… have an unique texture.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They are bumpy, high frequency, turbulent yet not much was done, during the time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Day in and day out, going through the motions in an endless ocean… Sinking deeper into an abyss, decorated by feelings of the heart. A recess into another world. An escape.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fate. Programming. DNA. Free Will. Choice. Young children, without order, without discipline, are wild, free, and chaotic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As time passes, experience envelopes, like growing trees, networks of neurons, a physical store, a container, a space growing, a metaphysical world, alone a child, looking down, crying, pain stitched across the face, from winter’s cold embrace.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There, a path required, for a cure desired, has sacrifices to be admired, and as vulnerable as a flower, for a series of hours, a coward, may choose to sour.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Truth seeps in, life’s restoring grace, so happenly, it’s encoded in our place. This place, few ever speak of, is full of life… maybe more than most, but it has no face, it is simply a ghost.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you see it, you will not know, it typically shows itself as your midnight hole. A house of wonder, you will not know, maybe there, you will see your midnight glow.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But if you are lucky, few dare seek. A fresh flow, you.. will.. meet&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>L</name></author><category term="Poetry" /><category term="Snapshot Story" /><summary type="html">Here’s a poem, I wrote… about dark memories long ago. If you care to read it, I suggest you read it, very… very… slow. Memories of years spent in total darkness… have an unique texture. They are bumpy, high frequency, turbulent yet not much was done, during the time. Day in and day out, going through the motions in an endless ocean… Sinking deeper into an abyss, decorated by feelings of the heart. A recess into another world. An escape. Fate. Programming. DNA. Free Will. Choice. Young children, without order, without discipline, are wild, free, and chaotic. As time passes, experience envelopes, like growing trees, networks of neurons, a physical store, a container, a space growing, a metaphysical world, alone a child, looking down, crying, pain stitched across the face, from winter’s cold embrace. There, a path required, for a cure desired, has sacrifices to be admired, and as vulnerable as a flower, for a series of hours, a coward, may choose to sour. Truth seeps in, life’s restoring grace, so happenly, it’s encoded in our place. This place, few ever speak of, is full of life… maybe more than most, but it has no face, it is simply a ghost. When you see it, you will not know, it typically shows itself as your midnight hole. A house of wonder, you will not know, maybe there, you will see your midnight glow. But if you are lucky, few dare seek. A fresh flow, you.. will.. meet</summary></entry></feed>